New York, concrete jungle
where dreams are made of.
If you can make it here,
you can make it anywhere.
It's up to you, if you have
a New York state of mind.
They say there are 8 million
stories in the naked city,
and you're about to see mine.
You see, it all started--
Well, I could show you
better than I can tell you,
and since it's about to start,
I'll just shut up now.
Pete, would you like
to share today?
Hi, I'm Pete,
and I am a workaholic.
Hi, Pete.
You know, this is a safe space.
I'm still struggling with this.
I just really like my job.
It's like this last assignment,
the boss sent me to Vegas.
I know I could have said no,
hell, I probably should have.
There were other places
I was supposed to be.
But when I work, man,
there's a charge, you know?
Pete.
I feel...
I feel alive.
Like nothing else exists.
You've got the fate of
another person in your hands.
I know you-- you doctors
and lawyers here, you feel me.
In those moments, nothing
should be more important.
But sometimes when I get
that call, I want to say no,
I just can't.
If I could do the job
better than anyone else, well,
how do I just walk away?
That's all I got.
Keep comin' back.
Sir?
Answer it.
Boss, we got a problem.
No shit.
We found a bug.
Where?
Right there in the Cubanos.
It's gotta be
the fucking cartel.
No way. Angel wouldn't dare.
She is one crazy bitch.
Oh, God. There's three of you.
Yeah, boss. We're all here.
Angel knows I won't break
the code, even for my own son.
Now, if there's cause...
This could be it, boss.
Who was last seen in my office?
- Pete.
- No way.
I saw him leave.
Yeah, I was with him.
So you were there after?
Whoa. What are you saying?
Tut-tut-tut-tut. Boss.
I want you to bring him to me.
Uh, boss, just to be clear,
do you mean--
Find Pete Stryker.
Hey, Pete. You okay?
Ah, I'm trying, man. I'm trying.
How are things with Mora?
She still won't talk to me.
Doesn't think I'll ever change.
We only can change as much
as we decide to.
That's up to us.
But you have to want
it for yourself.
Maybe that's just it.
I don't know if I do.
One day at a time, Pete.
See ya.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Listen to me. Nobody kills him.
Right now,
I need him alive to talk.
Do whatever you have to do
to get it out of him.
I need to know what he's done.
Hey, Reaper, my guy.
Man, you know I don't like
being called that.
Yeah, I know.
But from a business perspective,
it really tells us
everything we need to know.
You know, it's funny you
say that.
What part?
The talking part.
I didn't say anything
about talking.
You talk or you pay.
I'm super confused here
because I am talking.
Oh, shit!
You fucking baby. "Oh, shit."
You know why that scare you?
-Because it would hurt?
-No!
No?
Two words, dodgeball.
Oh, shit, man.
Look, hey, I'm sorry.
-I forgot.
-No, no, no, no.
You-- you no fucking forget.
You fucking lie.
You know what? You're right.
I-- I fucking lie. I no forget.
I'm sorry. I'm mirroring you.
I hate when I do that.
Lo-- look, I'm just not
gonna join a-- an adult
dodgeball league.
I mean, I did that as a kid.
It's real sport, professional,
da?
Da.
National Dodgeball League.
Stop.
They have Dodgeball
World Championships
on television.
Come on, man. It's a kids game.
Jesus!
See? You can't dodge.
Maybe better if you don't play.
You got your guys holding
me down.
No difference. Reaper could do.
You know you just referred
to yourself as Reaper, right?
Look, I'm sorry.
I will make it to one of
your games and take part, okay?
Well, no.
It-- it's too late now.
No, no, no, no. Come on, Reap.
I'm-- I'm serious.
I will make it.
I will show.
Man, you never fucking show,
ever.
I ask you, as my fucking friend,
to be there for me,
to help my team.
We work very hard to make
it to big leagues.
Hill runs, drills,
real rocky shit.
But no, you, you are too busy
and fancy in three-piece suit
and fancy shoes to come.
Plus, you always make fun.
You make fun all the time.
"Ha-ha-ha."
Make fun every time.
You're right.
I thought it was a dumbass
game you were playing,
so kill me.
No, don't kill me.
Look, I'm j-- I'm just--
I just didn't realize you
were so serious about it.
I will do better. Okay?
No, no, no, no.
I-- I do not fall for banana
in tailpipe.
You only care about you.
Now, you give up information,
you smelling mouse.
What the fuck are you
talkin' about?
And what the entire fuck
is goin' on here?
Seriously, guys,
I don't know what's wrong
with you right now,
but clearly you got some
fucked up intel.
Come on, he's one guy!
Uh, does that hurt?
It looks like it really hurts.
Um, it's nothing.
I don't know.
I think you should really
get that looked at.
As soon as you talk,
fucking mouse man.
Why do you keep calling me that?
Look, why don't we just
call Acardo
and straighten this?
Seriously, you need to really
do somethin' about that.
Don't move.
That was hardcore.
You broke rules, asshole.
Wait, wait.
Are you talkin' about
my support group?
Are you-- Look, I--
I know it's unconventional,
but I just needed a--
a safe space to work through
my feelings.
You betray family!
No, no. I just talk about
needing work-life balance.
What are you talking about?
-What are you talkin' about?
-What are you talking about?
What are you talkin' about?
You are snitch!
Wait, rat. You meant rat.
I know you very long time,
and you are asshole,
but I never thought you
would fuck family up
the asshole.
Reaper, now I--
I swear to Beyonce,
I would never turn.
Somebody got it wrong.
Acardo no think so.
Look, why don't we just call
the man and straighten this out?
Enough bullshit! Talk!
I'm feeling unsafe to share.
You know, whole fucking
family is after tiny
fucking mouse man who smell
very bad, and others,
they may not be so nice.
You know how they get. Plus--
Plus, the money.
-The money?
-Da, the...
Uh, suka.
No, fuck.
911, what's your emergency?
Uh, yeah, help, help.
a big head gash.
Bloody, bloody.
I, uh, I pass out, uh,
unconscious.
Oh, no. Thanks.
What are you doin' here, Pete?
Aw, sweetie, I missed you, too.
Well, I had a bit of
a rough meeting.
-Clearly.
-Uh-huh.
And after the meeting,
I really needed a drink.
Lots of bars in town.
And I really wanted to see you.
We're on a break, Pete.
I know, I know,
but I just needed...
There it is.
There what is?
Why you actually came here.
You want something as usual.
-No.
-Oh, you don't?
No.
It-- it's-- it's more like I--
Ugh.
Fuckin' unbelievable.
Um, you mind? Could I...
Of course, Pete.
Barge into my establishment
while we're on a break
because you need my help.
Yeah, 40-year-old scotch
work for you?
I'm in pain here, Mora.
We're supposed to kill
the assholes,
not become the assholes.
So who'd you piss off this time?
Literally could be
so, so many people.
-People like me.
-Oh, no, they don't.
You're just sayin'
that because you're mad.
You're right. I am mad
because I don't like you.
Well, you used to like me
quite a lot.
No.
I used to love you quite a lot.
But that was before
I realized that nothin'
or no one matters more
to you than the job.
Now, you know that's not fair.
Oh, take a look in the mirror,
Pete.
Life's not fair.
Huh.
Well, I pissed off your
father apparently.
-What?
-Mm-hmm.
He thinks I'm a fuckin' rat.
-You?
-Right?
Oh, you don't have it in you.
No, I'm not that fuckin' guy.
But wait, wait, wha--
what do you mean?
So that explains the lump
on your head.
Reaper and his guys
came to see me.
And you decided to show up
here knowing my father
sent people for you?
No, I decided to show up here
because I needed
someone I could trust.
No, you decided to show up
because you wanted to use me
to get to my dad.
You know what I can trust
about you, Pete?
That you're gonna
bring trouble
right to my fuckin' door.
No, I'm not.
Oh, really?
How did my last bar end up?
That wasn't my fault.
Right.
You just showed up to say
hi while being chased
by the 76th.
Oh, kind of like tonight, right?
I don't think I
was followed here.
Bar's closed. Everybody out.
All right. All right, we got it.
- Yeah, hurry up. Guys, come on.
- Ah, goddamn.
Not again.
You know, I really,
really love this place.
It's an impeccable atmosphere.
I'm not gonna let you ruin it
like you ruin everything else.
What's that supposed to mean?
Why don't you ask him?
Peter Stryker.
Señora.
Dead one,
any chance you can just drag
him out of here?
If he's willing to come.
Well, hell no, Muerto.
I actually hate you.
Remember, we don't say
things out of anger.
Oh, you're stupid.
And I hate, hate, hate you.
How, how is it that you guys
get all the cool names,
like Reaper and Muerto,
and I don't get a cool name?
I'm just Pete.
I don't even look like a Pete.
You want a fucking name?
I got a fucking name for you.
Oh, let me guess.
Rat.
Listen to me. I am not a rat.
I'm-- I'm not a rat, okay?
Man, have I ever lied to you?
Hmm.
Why don't you think about that?
I mean, really, really
think about that.
Is this about your
daughter's quinceañera?
That was fucking hurtful, man!
Why are all these assassins
so goddamn sensitive?
Listen, you know I would
have made it.
I just got held up
burying a body.
Oh, that tired old excuse?
No, no, it's true!
Ana had her hair
done beautifully,
a gorgeous white dress.
I really, really tried, man.
We had a place set for you.
I made him dig as fast
as he could.
Even an embossed place card.
He was just a little short guy
with little tiny arms.
You know we have to pay by
the fucking plate, right?
Yeah, you're a dick who
does mean things,
and I no longer like you.
But that makes no difference.
Acardo wants you brought in.
Babe.
Didn't you tell me how much
you love this shit?
-Not this shit.
-Tut-tut-tut-tut-tut-tut.
Save the lover's quarrel
for later.
Listen, Deathie, I don't
care what you do to bring
him in, okay?
Daddy gets what Daddy wants.
But you are not gonna fuck up
my bar doin' it.
I'm sorry, Mora,
but I don't make the rules.
You're right. In here, I do.
Rise, motherfucker.
Not my fuckin' bar!
Babe, I totally had that.
I'm glad you find it so amusing,
but at the end of the day,
this old relic here could
kill you just as dead as
any other gun.
Not with no bullets in it.
She already fired six.
Surprise, motherfucker.
Shut up, Muerto.
Seven shots, not six.
You are such a fuckin' asshole.
Can you please make the call
so we can find out
what the hell is goin' on here?
You want me to call my dad
about you?
Would be nice.
-Why?
-So I don't die.
You're not gonna die. He
wants to interrogate you first.
First?
Now, you and I both know
how that could go.
People get overzealous.
True.
And you're just gonna let
that happen?
Yep. This is on you.
I don't know if you're a rat,
maybe you are.
How could you even say that
with as many bodies as I've
put in the ground
for this family?
Maybe you got caught
and this is your way out.
I would never do that to you
or your d--
Can you-- do you mind?
I love this family too much.
No.
Pete, what you love more
than anything is this life.
Okay?
It makes you who you are.
You'd be nothing inside
without it.
You're not a rat.
Thank you.
That's why you need to call him.
No.
Mora, come on.
Look, Pete,
your addiction
to the work, the-- the life,
it's costing you everything
you should care about.
I'm not helping you fix it
this time.
You clean up your own mess.
I'm done.
Fine. Fine.
Start with him.
Here.
You need to stop the bleeding,
and I'm sorry about
your daughter's quinceañera.
You're welcome.
And where are you off to now?
Well, I'm gonna go see Thanatos.
Oh, good.
Yeah, go fuck up more
people's lives,
sounds about right.
Well, he's gonna care enough
to help me.
Or hopefully shoot you
in the face.
Musgrove, I need a cleanup.
Yeah, Pete was here. Just left.
Uh, hey, buddy.
Uh, you wanna turn down
the music?
Um, can you turn down--
Peter.
Mingjue.
This season is next level.
Oh, go fuck yourself.
Well, that's just rude.
Really?
Is it as rude as missing
my first ever fashion show?
Look, I-- I tried to get there.
No, you didn't.
Muerto told me.
You took a job.
Well, Acardo asked me--
He asked several of us.
You accepted when you knew
you were walking
in my fashion show!
You're right.
I made a mistake.
A mistake?
You wanna know
what a mistake was?
Trusting that you would
show up for me.
Look, I'm sorry, man.
Ah, you as sorry as I was?
Hmm?
Watching that poor model
walk down the runway
in your suit?
Do you know how many
yards of Guanashina
it took to fit you?
A lot.
You were my finale.
Thousands and thousands
of dollars, hours upon hours
of work.
That was the big,
final moment to end my show.
But no.
I had the kid from the end
of Big tripping down my runway
in his own damn pants.
I'm so sorry.
Everyone laughed.
You know, I had to pretend
like it was on purpose.
But-- But I remember you
got some good reviews, right?
Uh, they said that you
are skewering
the seriousness of fashion.
Oh, like, oh my God,
I should thank you?
Well, you don't have to.
Maybe I should thank you.
That Fall '23 suit collection
of yours
with the blood stain-resistant
material saved my ass, man.
I was in an elevator
and these two guys--
God, Pete, shut up!
You are a terrible
fucking friend!
And the fact that the rat
is you just makes perfect sense.
You care about no one
but yourself, ever.
That's not true.
It's Pete first, the rest of
the world second or third
-or fourth or--
-I-- I get it. I get it.
But look, man, I would
never turn on you guys.
No? Not even to save yourself?
No.
You know, I might believe you.
Well, thank you.
'Cause you wanna go down
as the best, and you know
Thanatos is right on your heels.
Oh, come on,
got to figure-- No, no.
And your weak, oversized ego
couldn't bear being shamed.
First of all, Than is nowhere
near my numbers.
Oh, but he has
an elegant finesse.
Oh, bullshit.
And secondly, what the fuck
does everyone think I did?
Huh?
And how much is Acardo
paying you guys to take me out?
It is not to take you out.
It's to bring you in.
What's the difference?
Once I'm in, how the fuck do
I prove that I'm innocent?
Hmm.
You don't.
Acardo will just torture
you until you give him
what he wants.
And when I can't, I'm dead.
No, thank you.
Now answer my question.
Oh.
Uh, you just--
You asked two questions.
Oh, right. Uh, 500K.
That's it?
After all I've done
for this family?
That's the thing, Pete.
Why, after all you've done,
would you choose to betray
them this way?
Look, like I told Reaper--
and how is he, by the way?
Look, I told him that I was
just going to a therapy group.
Okay?
I know we're supposed to be
in the circle of secrecy
and all that, but I needed
someone I could talk to.
All right?
And I'm very discreet,
no details, just my feelings.
Feelings.
Oh, you're gonna have to
take that up with Acardo.
I do not call the shots,
old friend.
Well, maybe you could
call Acardo.
I don't wanna hurt you, man.
We go back a long way.
We got a lot of history.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don't you even think about it.
Those suits are bespoke.
I will kill you my goddamn self
this time if you ruin my work.
Now don't test me, Pete.
You remember what my name
means, right?
Your name means what
everybody else's name means.
Death.
But do you remember
what my name is?
Pete. Just Pete, right?
N-- n-- no. Um, my last name.
Stryker, motherfucker.
Damn it, Pete!
You're hurting me!
Fuck you, Pete!
Fuck!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, buddy.
Don't you fuckin' buddy me,
you piece of shit.
Has everyone lost their minds?
It's me, your best friend,
little Jenny's godfather.
Shut your fuckin' mouth.
I helped her make cookies
for the bake sale.
I don't wanna hear your
fuckin' bullshit, man.
-You are such a f--
You know I love you, man.
That's why you show up at
my place with the whole
fuckin' city after you, huh?
I need some answers.
Well, you could call.
My phone isn't, uh,
great right now.
So you show up here not givin'
a shit about anybody
-but yourself.
-Come on, man, that's not fair.
But it's accurate.
You didn't think what
comin' here might mean
for me and my family, did you?
Did you?
Do you really wanna play
this game?
Than, I swear, there's no game.
I just figured that you
would know why everyone
thinks I turned.
I don't know and I don't care.
I just follow orders,
unlike yourself.
Come on, Than. You know me.
And I'm not a fucking rat.
Well, Acardo thinks you are.
Enough to put a bounty on
your head.
You wanna call that little shit
a bounty?
I mean, come on, 500K for me?
For all I know?
-Please.
-Consider yourself lucky.
If any more,
you'd be dead by now.
Yeah, maybe.
But look, if he really thought
I was an informant,
wouldn't he offer a shitload
of money?
I mean, come on, 500K is what
we got for No Nose McGillan.
You keep talkin',
I'll take you out for free.
The boss must've put out
a no-kill order
'cause no one has shot me yet.
Yeah, well, don't tempt me.
Now, is that because he thinks
I have intel or is it
because he's conflicted?
You know he has deep
feelings for me.
You are unfucking' believable,
you know that?
- Regardless, it's not true.
- I'm innocent.
See, I-- I joined a--
a support group for workaholics.
Uh-huh.
So the FBI's using
support groups as cover now,
huh?
See, now I know you lost
your mind.
I could say the same for you.
Fuckin' traitor.
How you like it?
Did you just bitch slap me?
Yep.
That's Janice.
It's Janice.
This is a dick move.
Hey, babe.
What? No, I'm good.
Yeah, I'm just--
I'm just a little bit out
of breath is all.
No, no, Pete, he stopped by
for a quick workout.
What?
Oh, come on, don't be silly.
No, I-- I s-- babe, I swear.
Hey.
Uh, he's not with another
woman this time.
Honey, he's joking.
You heard his voice.
What?
- I...
- No, you don't need to come here.
No, it's fine.
I'll meet you at home.
Yeah, yeah, I'll grab it on
the way.
Sure.
Mm-hmm, I love your meatloaf.
No, you don't.
No. Okay.
Can--
I-- I really gotta go, honey.
Mm, look, my set's up, okay?
Babe, of course you're
more important than a set.
I just-- I'd like to get--
Yes. Okay.
-Say bye, Pete.
-Bye, Janice!
Uh, gi--
give Jenny a hug for me.
There's no women here.
Would you stop?
-What?
-Honey, he's joking, I swear.
Yes, I love you, too. Bye.
- Come on.
- What?
That's not funny.
We are just gettin' over this.
Hey, don't get mad at me
for your past indiscretions.
-Shit, it wasn't me.
-Excuse me?
After everything we've
been through?
After all this family did
for you?
I swear, I would never turn.
You know how many times
we invited you into our home,
you never show up?
Or Jenny's plays
or Tommy's science fair?
You know--
They wait for their Uncle Pete.
They watch the fuckin' door,
man!
You never show!
When Janice was in
the hospital...
I sent flowers.
That's not good enough, man.
You matter to us.
You matter to me.
Than, I'm sorry.
Look, if you're telling
the truth, you better find
a way to make this right
with Acardo.
That is the only way out
of this.
I will.
No, you probably won't.
Hey, Pete, you know why no one
makes you meatloaf?
'Cause you never fail to
let down the people you love.
Give you 24 hours,
then I'm comin' for you myself.
Friend or not, I'm not
goin' down for you.
I got a family to protect.
That's something you'll
never know anything about.
I don't like meatloaf anyhow.
Fuck!
Sit or lie comfortably.
Quietly.
Allow yourself to be here fully.
Gradually let the horse shit
of the external world fade
from your awareness.
If you find your mind
wandering to other thoughts,
just acknowledge that all
that shit is fucking bullshit.
You're here now, in the realm
of possibility.
Don't answer that.
Hello, again.
You gotta be fuckin' kidding me.
Hey, wait, hang on a second,
Pete.
Hang on, hang on, hang on.
Um...
Oh my God.
What?
No, Mora, I'm fine.
Thanks for asking.
Are you trying to
wreck everything I love?
You mean me or the couch?
Oh, and Thanatos is fine, too.
Not that you care.
I wasn't worried about Than.
Oh, really?
Well, he's legendary, so...
You said I was legendary.
There was a time.
So what you saying?
I'm saying life moves on, Pete.
For who? You?
I suppose.
Oh, so that's it?
That's it.
Hmm.
You know, you're in this just
as much as I am,
and you know it.
No one is in it as much
as you are, Pete.
Take a look around you.
We all have family,
passions, friendships
that have nothing
to do with the life.
We're all out here livin'
while you drown in this idea
of being the best
knock-around guy
the family ever had.
But you forget, one day
you'll be dead.
We'll all be dead.
And maybe... maybe people
will remember your name.
That's all I want.
I know.
It's just the rest of us
want more.
We wanna know we mattered
more than just a body count.
And now I know that's
something you'll just
never understand.
Can't I have both?
No, you can't.
-Mora, listen.
-Just stop talkin'.
No, no, no, no, look.
-Please, Pete.
-I'm serious.
-I mean it.
-I'm serious. Hear me out.
Now, Mora, I know
that you love--
Are you fucking kidding--
So Pete, how are things at work?
Not great.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
What's goin' on?
Downsizing.
My organization has decided
to eliminate
one of the employees.
Someone you know personally?
It's me, Roger.
I'm the downsize.
Mm, I see.
How does that make you feel?
How does it make me feel?
Well, I'm feeling pretty
beaten up about it, clearly.
Okay. Do you care to
expand on that situation a bit?
Well, everyone's trying
to kill me, so...
So what can we do to
help support you through this?
I don't know. You got any guns?
You know this is a safe space,
Pete.
Not for long, because
everybody in the goddamn
family is coming down here
to kill me, right now.
Well, sounds to me as if
you're jeopardizing
the energy of our little group,
Pete, so...
You self-centered motherfucker!
Let's kill him.
-Wait, what?
-No, I think he's right.
Everyone, you wanna grab
your weapons?
-Let's go.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Safe space, safe space,
safe space, safe space!
You blow-darted me.
Yes. Yes, I did.
I feel violated.
Well, you didn't start yelling
"safe space" until after,
so...
And you're welcome, by the way.
Yeah. Thanks.
You do good work.
Ah, you idiots give me a lot
of practice.
You know you said that,
like, plural?
News flash,
I'm fourth generation
in the family enterprise.
You're not the first,
nor will you be the last moron
I have to deal with.
Well, I'm just sayin'
I haven't been seeing
anybody out of respect.
Respect?
You trash my bar,
then you show up here all
bleedy and needy,
and you wanna talk to me
about respect?
Well, we said we'd always
be there for each other.
Oh, please.
You're just using me
to get yourself out
of the current mess you've
made.
You're exploiting
my codependent nature.
Wait.
Are you in the program?
Maybe.
Well, babe, that's amazing.
No, I'm detaching with love.
You just said love.
After detaching.
You still love me.
-No, I hate you.
-Yes, you do.
-You still love me, just say it.
No.
Please pardon the intrusion,
Mora.
You just broke down
my fuckin' door.
Uh, well, I do apologize,
but I'm here on behalf
of her father.
He's worried you might
be in danger.
I am, of contagious idiocy.
Come on, Mora.
Take him away, Gabriel.
He's all yours.
What? Wha--
What the fuck?
Pete. Oh!
No, wait!
What a fuckin' asshole.
Oh my God.
I hate you so much.
No, you don't.
You still love me.
So say it.
No.
You know you want to.
I really don't.
Mora, you saved me.
I saved my place, that's all.
No, you did it because you
love me.
So, I'm gonna say it.
Mora, I--
No. No, no, no.
Mora, I love you.
I love you,
and I've never stopped.
I wanna start a family with you.
I want a life.
I just don't know how to stop.
This is just really, really fun.
Oh, you haven't even worked
step one.
Which one is that?
Jesus, do you even go?
- Yeah.
- I just leave early sometimes.
It's the one where you
admit that you're powerless
and your life is unmanageable,
leaving you irritable
and restless.
Powerless and unmanageable,
right.
Ugh, you're never gonna change,
Pete,
not until you
want it bad enough.
I want you bad enough.
Y-- you can't change for me
or anyone else.
You have to deal with yourself,
figure out what hole
you're tryin' to fill with
all this.
That's what she said.
You're such a deflecting idiot.
See? You love me, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
But not more than I love myself.
So, Mora, how do I make
it right?
Step one.
Call my dad.
Call me old-fashioned,
it should be so simple.
I put out an order,
and the order gets done.
Instead, I have you
fucking idiots on my couch.
Now, how is that possible?
Hmm?
He's one fucking guy,
and you're supposed
to be the best I got.
Pete is the best.
I'd go Thanatos.
It's too close to call.
But Pete has body count,
like, very big body count.
Yeah, but Thanatos,
he's got style.
- He's like the Brando of bodies.
- True.
But-- but Pete,
he's like MacGyver.
MacGyver fix everything.
Who cares about MacGyver?
No, it's t-- no, no,
it's too tough to call.
-He-- he fix everything.
-What are you talking about?
Apples and oranges.
It's Selena and Celine Dion.
What are you talkin' about,
apples and oranges?
Just silence!
Jesus Christ.
The traitor is out there,
and I sent you
three to do a job.
One job!
Instead, I got Musgrove
runnin' all over the city
on cleanup duty.
But to be fair, when I
fought him, Mora was there.
Man, she's fuckin' scary.
That's true.
My daughter is quite dangerous.
She shot off my fucking leg!
Well, she takes after
her old man.
Si.
Agreed.
You're not as worthless
and embarrassing as these two.
-Yeah.
-Oh, you think that's funny?
-Chill.
-Thank you, sir.
My baby girl.
No, no, I-- I'm--
I'm with Muerto over here.
Lovely work, my dear.
Tell me, did Gabriel save
you from that lunatic?
Yeah, afraid not, Daddy.
That piece of shit,
if he hurts you...
No, no.
Daddy, Daddy, it's okay.
He just wants to talk to you.
He should talk to the fishes.
Put that fucking rat on.
Boss?
You,
after everything I've done.
Bringing you in when you
were just a wet, lonely stray
on the street, giving you a
job, giving you a family!
I was hoping to give you
my daughter's hand.
I thought you would give
me my heirs.
But to be betrayed
by my almost son,
it's too much to bear.
I trusted you, Peter.
And I would never betray
that trust, sir.
I don't know who put it on
the street, but it's a lie.
I love this family.
I love your daughter.
I would never do anything
to hurt either of you.
Though I must say,
I was a little hurt myself.
Excuse me?
I mean, 500K for all the bodies
I put in the ground,
and all of that I know,
I mean, come on.
I mean, that seems just
a little,
well, insulting really.
Have you lost your
fucking mind?
No, sir. I just assumed that--
You want me to raise it?
Is that it?
No, I'm not saying that.
You listen to me.
You remember who you're
talking to?
I've dropped men for less.
You don't wanna test me, Peter.
No, sir, I don't.
But I swear to you,
I am not a rat.
Then prove it.
You have till sunrise.
And then I raise the price,
and the stakes,
every hour you fail.
If you think you could bring
me down,
you are fucking mistaken.
N-- no.
Hey, Daddy.
I hung up without
saying goodbye.
That was rude. I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Kiss, kiss, love, love, Daddy.
Kiss, kiss, love, love.
You never stop proving
you're an idiot.
Well, how do I prove
that I'm not a rat by sunrise?
God, you'd have to take
out someone like Angel
to pull that off.
That's perfect.
I was fuckin' kidding.
No, no, no.
No informant would ever
dare take out a rival boss.
Yeah, because they'd be
starting a war, you moron.
-That's the only way.
-Can't you kill someone else?
I don't know. Like-- like him?
What? Uh, no, I can't kill him.
We love him.
Plus, he's worthless.
No one would care.
-True.
-Hey!
But that plan is insanity.
I mean, come on.
Her right-hand man, Pequiño?
Yeah, that's a stupid name.
But what other choice do I have?
Uh, none.
Fuck! Let's do it.
You just said let's.
Oh, shut up.
Okay.
Such a thing of beauty.
Some girls get ponies
from their daddy.
I get knock-around guys
and guns.
Oh, this is such a bad idea.
I'll infield from the roof.
Got your six.
Things get too rough,
I'll call my dad.
Although, you'll probably be
dead by the time help arrives,
but at least
he'll know you're one
of the good ones.
Yeah. Thanks.
Go get 'em, killer.
We got four on foot,
two on the roof,
and others in and out.
You're welcome.
Thanks, babe.
You've never played this before?
Let me try, let me try.
All right, go ahead.
I already heard you once.
All right, all right.
Wow!
I'm even movin' my head on
nothin'.
Like, he's like...
Okay, feel-- feel the technique,
feel the technique.
- I don't know what to do anymore.
- You're not listening.
- It's not there.
I can't-- I can't do it.
All right. It's all connected.
There you go.
whole thing.
You try.
Okay.
That's how it's done.
There we go.
Oh.
you try.
Okay.
Oh my God.
You weren't listening.
Wait? That's how you do it?
Yeah,
that's how it's really done.
All right. Okay. N-- no.
Oh, dick!
Let me go again.
All right. Okay.
All right.
No, you-- you gotta use
the whole neck.
- All right.
- I'm trying, I'm trying.
You need some help
with somethin', Acardo?
Pequiño.
Let's go, Mora.
Would you like some tea, Mora?
I'd prefer something stronger
if you have it, personally.
That's right.
You run a bar.
You are an entrepreneur,
just like myself.
I don't know that I'd put us
on the same scale,
but I do love my business.
You could have fallen
in line like the rest
of the women in your family,
disappeared in the shadows.
But I admire your ambition.
You took on your whole family
and seized power.
It takes a lot more
than ambition.
You have no idea.
It makes me really wonder
why you would risk coming here
to my place in such
a disrespectful way.
Technically, I was across
the street minding
my own business.
Then why?
Does it have something
to do with that informant
boyfriend of yours?
-Uh, he's not my--
-Then why?
Your father and I,
we've been able to keep
the peace despite
our differences.
You mean your running fentanyl.
It's just a revenue stream.
It's no different than
what you're doing.
Don't compare us to you.
That shit is as dirty as
it comes, and you know it.
Perhaps.
But we all deal in death
though in one way or another,
wouldn't you agree?
Hmm.
Do you think your brother
would agree?
I'm sorry about him, by the way,
but it really had nothing
to do with us.
He was just a customer,
same as everybody else.
He wasn't just like anyone else.
He was mine.
Oh.
Revenge.
So easy.
Like I said, I was across
the street minding my
own business when man bun
over here grabbed me.
Right.
Victim thinking is so
unbecoming of a strong woman,
don't you think?
Well, either way,
I don't think my father
would appreciate it.
Do you know what it would
be like if our families went
to war?
I do. Do you?
I don't think either of us
would like it very much.
Only a crazy person would.
Do you know what the men
call us?
Crazy bitches.
How crazy are you?
You're fuckin' up my house,
and I don't like that.
Completely sympathize.
I can't say that this is going
exactly to plan.
Not sure what you mean.
Well, I may have put
the word out that Pete Stryker
has turned.
To destabilize our organization,
you were gonna make your move.
Your father's never gonna
stop blaming me
for your brother's death.
He'd have come for me sooner
or later.
But I can't say that you
two idiots coming to my house
hasn't made it a whole
lot easier for me.
I think you underestimate
how much Pete loves his job.
Yeah, well, I don't think
I've underestimated how
much Pete loves you.
Shit.
Your father, if he could've
just moved on,
we could've avoided this
entire mess.
It's really such a pity.
See, that's where you're wrong.
Tell me.
The only pity is that we let
you live this long.
Really?
Really.
You fucking bitch.
Who's the victim now, bitch?
Hey, what do you think?
Oh, fuck yeah.
Mm.
-Mm.
You know we're gonna need
proof of kill, right?
I'm pretty sure the
whole world's gonna know
about it.
Come on, for my dad.
Okay.
Let's get the fuck outta here.
Let's.
We make a pretty good team.
Yeah, we do.
Be a shame to give up on us now.
You're the best, Pete.
Why quit when you're the best?
For you, I would.
Make you crazy
not to be in the game.
Come on, let's not go overboard.
Mm.
On the flip side,
here's a interesting thought.
You and me against the world,
going up against all kinds
of domestic
and international assholes.
Ah.
Well, that's kind of exciting.
But you know what else is?
Balance.
Like wakin' up slow on
a Sunday morning
or watchin' a movie
on a Friday night,
having dinner across the table
from the one you love.
That's what's truly exciting,
Pete,
when you grow up and want more.
I wanna try.
No, no, Mora, Mora, I'm serious.
Not for you or anyone else,
but for me.
I want my life to matter.
I don't wanna be just some
stat on a mob sheet.
There you two are.
We took out Angel, sir, for you.
I knew you would.
Well, as soon as the word
hit the street about you
being dirty, I knew it
was bullshit.
W-- why did you put
a hit out on me?
We're always goin' to
have people that doubt you
if you don't prove you're clean.
It would make the organization
look weak
if we didn't make you
answer for it.
And weakness is...
Is the kiss of death.
But-- but-- but why didn't
you just tell me?
Because you and everyone else,
including my little
munchkin here,
had to believe it was real.
It was the only way to end it.
To end Angel.
So, you knew I would go
after her?
Well, I knew you'd go
to Mora for help,
you always do.
And I know my daughter,
and she's smart.
She knew it would take
something big to prove
you're clean.
Plus, she hates Angel as much
as I do.
So, you used him.
Hmm.
In all the best ways.
No other motherfucker in
our family is crazy enough
to do what he just did.
And it allows you
deniability while you get
her shit off the streets.
Genius, Daddy.
-Thank you.
-Really?
I also did it for the both
of you.
Peter, you've been throwing
your life away.
You've been losing the love
and respect of everyone
in this family.
But more importantly,
you've been losing my daughter
who loves you very much.
And if her mother is anything
to go by,
nothing is worth that.
But, sir, you almost got
me killed, like, 23 times.
Yeah, you know,
I was in there, too.
Ah, I had no fear.
You're a viper, my darling.
And Peter,
you didn't die
because you are the greatest.
You're the most talented
cleaner I've ever seen.
You're strong, you're smart,
you're sensitive.
But there's more to life
than that, my boy.
If I had Mora's mother
and brother back, oh,
what I would do differently?
Uh...
you know, tonight
has made me look at things
pretty differently.
You are so welcome.
I wanna do better.
And?
And I want us to be together
as a family and make it work.
No more disappearin'.
And no more trash in my place.
Well, maybe I could be a--
an instructor of something.
-An instructor?
-Yeah.
What, like a killin' instructor?
I don't know if that's a thing,
babe.
Well, whatever it is,
I wanna make it work.
I am powerless and my life
has become unmanageable.
Let's see what we can do.
- And just like that,
- I now wanted the corny shit
in life.
Long walks in the park.
Little fifi dogs
who are feminine.
And beige children.
This is exactly what
our relationship needed,
to reconnect doin' the things
we love that brought us
together in the first place.
A rekindling, if you will.
And that hasn't happened
for the longest time.
Church of Billy Joel.
And PS, the couple that
slays together, stays together.
Now, that's Pete Stryker.
Hi. My name is Pete
and I'm a workaholic.
Things are great.
I finally found some
work-life balance.
Maybe still a little too
much work, but--
Remember, Mora, no crosstalk.
Okay?
Right. Sorry.
I realize now that I wasn't
just letting down the people
I love, I was letting
myself down.
I was chasing meaning
through notoriety
and admiration, and in the end,
that's all just meaningless.
Meaningless? Really?
Liliana.
-Crosstalk.
-Shut up, Roger.
Okay, Liliana, maybe we
just need to refresh on
the rules.
You wanna talk about rules,
motherfucker?
Oh.
Those two broke
the fucking family rules,
-and he calls it meaningless?
-Babe, remember my dream?
Well, it means something to me.
It was just like this,
but everybody was armed.
You took down my boss
with no provocation,
and now you have to pay.
Wait a minute,
did you work for Angel?
I did, until you put her
in the ground.
Now, I can see how
these situations can feel
like life or death,
but let's not let our work--
Oh, shut up, Roger.
So, you think she
brought company?
-Shit.
-Yeah.